Amirhossein Khodaei

Web Developer

🚱 amirhosseinkhodaei.ir

@ amir76_kh@yahoo.com

+989120126656

5 in





About Me

Hi! I'm a Web Developer, currently working as Front-End Developer at SnappCarFix, the largest online platform for car parts and services in Iran. I have around 1 years of experience in software development mainly in Web Development. I'm a self-learner, without prejudice on tools and tech stacks, and ready for new challenges.

• Marriage: Single

• Education: Master. Information Security Engineering

Military Service: Exempted
 Birth Date: 18 March 1998

Educations

• Master - Malek Ashtar University of Technology

Information Security 2021 - present

Software engineering 2018 - 2021

Bachelor - Islamic Azad University of Isfahan

Skills

In summary, i have experience working with these tools and often use them:

• Keact

HTML/CSS

Responsive Design

• GitHub/GitLab CI/CD

Linux Servers

Bootstrap

Redux

• Laravel

• CSS Module • axios

Antd

• MvSOL Database Managment

• Docker

Routing

• JS • Sass

Wordpress

• Material UI

• Web Crawling

Experiences

FrontEnd - Web Developer

SnappCarFix / CarFillo

React.js, Python, Wordpress,

March 2021 - present Isfahan, Iran Full-time

SnappCarFix is an online platform for Car parts and services, backed by Snapp (Uber clone). It includes web apps for Stores, ServiceCenters, Agents, and Sellers, to offer products/services like oil, battery, engine parts, car wash, etc, with 7 delivery/service solutions per product. CarFillo sells products to service centers, it's an Online Shop, which service centers gain credits here based on their services on SnappCarFix.

snappcarfix.com ag.snappcarfix.com sc.snappcarfix.com carfillo.com

Responsibilities:

- Develop and deliver platform
- Code cleaning and some times adding some features to the project.
- $\bullet\,$ Developed and structured the core module for React frontend projects
- Rewrite and developed callcenter panel project using React
 Developed a real-time web crawler with a attractive fronter
- Developed a real-time web crawler with a attractive frontend using python and react.js
- Implementing new features for website
- Implementing the graphical element according to the concept
- Managing projects on Gitlab
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.

FrontEnd - Web Developer

SnappCarFix / CarFillo

React.js, Python, Wordpress,

March 2021 - present Isfahan, Iran Full-time

SnappCarFix is an online platform for Car parts and services, backed by Snapp (Uber clone). It includes web apps for Stores, ServiceCenters, Agents, and Sellers, to offer products/services like oil, battery, engine parts, car wash, etc, with 7 delivery/service solutions per product. CarFillo sells products to service centers, it's an Online Shop, which service centers gain credits here based on their services on SnappCarFix.

snappcarfix.com ag.snappcarfix.com sc.snappcarfix.com carfillo.com

Responsibilities:

- Develop and deliver platform
- Code cleaning and some times adding some features to the project.
- Developed and structured the core module for React frontend projects
- Rewrite and developed callcenter panel project using React
- Developed a real-time web crawler with a attractive frontend using python and react.js
- Implementing new features for website
- Implementing the graphical element according to the concept
- Managing projects on Gitlab
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.

Projects

Check out my site & Github for projects.

amirhosseinkhodaei.ir/#Projects github.com/amirhosseinkhodaei